{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "In what year did The Baha Men release 'Who Let The Dogs Out'?",
      "answers": ["2000", "2010", "2007"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "In which year did Leonard Cohen release his album Ten New Songs?",
      "answers": ["2008", "2004", "2001"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Johnny Cash box set was released two months after his death in 2003?",
      "answers": ["The Legend", "Unearthed", "Sun"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What group sang the song 'Independent Woman'?",
      "answers": ["Destiny's Child", "Backstreet Boys", "TLC"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What group sang the song 'Fell in Love with a Girl'?",
      "answers": ["The Black Keys", "Green Day", "The White Stripes"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What song featured performances by Christina Aguilera, Lil' Kim, Mýa and Pink?",
      "answers": ["Lady Marmalade", "Bootylicious", "Can't hold us down"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is singer Justin Vernon better known as?",
      "answers": ["Bon Bon", "Bon Iver", "Bon Ivy"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Eminem's third album?",
      "answers": ["Here Comes Eminem", "Time For Eminem", "The Eminem Show"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who featured on the 2007 Timbaland hit 'Apologize'?",
      "answers": ["One Republic", "Backstreet Boys", "NSync"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who performed the 2003 hit 'Crazy in Love'?",
      "answers": ["Brittany Spears", "Beyoncé", "Pink"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Swing, Swing' was a hit for which band in this decade?",
      "answers": ["All American Rejects", "The White Stripes", "The Strokes"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": " Look at the stars, look how they shine for you' is the opening line of which Coldplay song?",
      "answers": ["Gold", "Blue", "Yellow"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Billboard named which of Mariah Carey's songs the biggest and most played of the 00s?",
      "answers": ["All I want for Christmas is you", "We belong together", "Always be my baby"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which female popstar hit the top spot in 2000 with 'What a Girl Wants'?",
      "answers": ["Christina Aguilera", "Brittany Spears", "Mariah Carey"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "In which year did Arcade Fire release their debut album?",
      "answers": ["2001", "2006", "2004"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Are You Gonna Be My Girl is a hit song for which Australian band?",
      "answers": ["You Am I", "Jet", "Powderfinger"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What reality TV star released the single 'Stars Are Blind' in 2006?",
      "answers": ["Paris Hilton", "Kelly Osbourne", "Tila Tequila"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "In 2008 Beyoncé released the album entitled 'I Am Sasha….'?",
      "answers": ["Feisty", "Nice", "Fierce"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who featured on Rihanna's smash hit 'Umbrella'?",
      "answers": ["Jay Z", "Eminem", "Akon"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Tim McGraw teamed up with which RnB artist on 'Over and Over'?",
      "answers": ["Usher", "Nelly", "50 Cent"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    }
  ]
 }
 